const SampleSet = {
  results: [
    {
      category: 'Science%20%26%20Nature',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'The%20%27Islets%20of%20Langerhans%27%20is%20found%20in%20which%20human%20organ%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Pancreas',
      incorrect_answers: ['Kidney', 'Liver', 'Brain'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Geography',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20one%20of%20the%20Neo-Aramaic%20languages%20spoken%20by%20the%20Jewish%20population%20from%20Northwestern%20Iraq%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Lishana%20Deni',
      incorrect_answers: [
        'Hulaul%C3%A1',
        'Lishan%20Didan',
        'Chaldean%20Neo-Aramaic',
      ],
    },
    {
      category: 'General%20Knowledge',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'Disney%27s%20Haunted%20Mansion%20is%20home%20to%20a%20trio%20of%20Hitchhiking%20Ghosts.%20Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20one%20of%20them%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Harry',
      incorrect_answers: ['Gus', 'Phineas', 'Ezra'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'What%20year%20was%20%22JoJo%27s%20Bizarre%20Adventure%3A%20Phantom%20Blood%22%20first%20released%3F',
      correct_answer: '1987',
      incorrect_answers: ['2013', '1983', '1995'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Animals',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question: 'What%20type%20of%20creature%20is%20a%20Bonobo%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Ape',
      incorrect_answers: ['Lion', 'Parrot', 'Wildcat'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Television',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'Who%20played%20the%20sun%20baby%20in%20the%20original%20run%20of%20Teletubbies%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Jessica%20Smith',
      incorrect_answers: [
        'Pui%20Fan%20Lee',
        'Sue%20Monroe',
        'Lisa%20Brockwell',
      ],
    },
    {
      category: 'Geography',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question: 'What%20is%20the%20Finnish%20word%20for%20%22Finland%22%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Suomi',
      incorrect_answers: ['Eesti', 'Magyarorsz%C3%A1g', 'Sverige'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Politics',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'Which%20of%20the%20following%20United%20States%20Presidents%20served%20the%20shortest%20term%20in%20office%3F',
      correct_answer: 'William%20Henry%20Harrison',
      incorrect_answers: [
        'Zachary%20Taylor',
        'James%20A.%20Garfield',
        'Warren%20G.%20Harding',
      ],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'The%20creeper%20in%20Minecraft%20was%20the%20result%20of%20a%20bug%20while%20implementing%20which%20creature%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Pig',
      incorrect_answers: ['Zombie', 'Chicken', 'Cow'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'Medaka%20Kurokami%20from%20%22Medaka%20Box%22%20has%20what%20abnormality%3F',
      correct_answer: 'The%20End',
      incorrect_answers: ['Perfection', 'Sandbox', 'Fairness'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Science%20%26%20Nature',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'What%20does%20the%20term%20%22isolation%22%20refer%20to%20in%20microbiology%3F',
      correct_answer:
        'The%20separation%20of%20a%20strain%20from%20a%20natural%2C%20mixed%20population%20of%20living%20microbes',
      incorrect_answers: [
        'A%20lack%20of%20nutrition%20in%20microenviroments',
        'The%20nitrogen%20level%20in%20soil',
        'Testing%20effects%20of%20certain%20microorganisms%20in%20an%20isolated%20enviroments%2C%20such%20as%20caves',
      ],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Film',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'In%20the%20%22Jurassic%20Park%22%20universe%2C%20when%20did%20%22Jurassic%20Park%3A%20San%20Diego%22%20begin%20construction%3F',
      correct_answer: '1985',
      incorrect_answers: ['1988', '1986', '1993'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Cartoon%20%26%20Animations',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'In%20%22Gravity%20Falls%22%2C%20what%20does%20Quentin%20Trembley%20do%20when%20he%20is%20driven%20out%20from%20the%20White%20House%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Eat%20a%20salamander%20and%20jump%20out%20the%20window.',
      incorrect_answers: [
        'Leave%20in%20peace.',
        'Jump%20out%20the%20window.',
        'Release%201%2C000%20captive%20salamanders%20into%20the%20white%20house.',
      ],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question: 'When%20was%20the%20Valve%20Corporation%20founded%3F',
      correct_answer: 'August%2024%2C%201996',
      incorrect_answers: [
        'December%2026%2C%201994',
        'March%2022%2C%201997',
        'March%2013%2C%201997',
      ],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'In%20%22Pok%C3%A9mon%20Sun%20and%20Moon%22%2C%20Team%20Skull%20took%20over%20which%20town%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Po%20Town',
      incorrect_answers: ['Heahea%20City', 'Tapu%20Village', 'Iki%20Town'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Books',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'In%20the%20Magic%3A%20The%20Gathering%20universe%2C%20which%20plane%20does%20the%20Homelands%20expansion%20take%20place%20in%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Ulgrotha',
      incorrect_answers: ['Bant', 'Llanowar', 'Tazeem'],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Cartoon%20%26%20Animations',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20Jonny%27s%20pet%20dog%20in%20The%20Adventures%20of%20Jonny%20Quest%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Bandit',
      incorrect_answers: ['Lucky', 'Rocky', 'Max'],
    },
    {
      category: 'General%20Knowledge',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'Located%20in%20Chile%2C%20El%20Teniente%20is%20the%20world%27s%20largest%20underground%20mine%20for%20what%20metal%3F',
      correct_answer: 'Copper',
      incorrect_answers: ['Iron', 'Nickel', 'Silver'],
    },
    {
      category: 'General%20Knowledge',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question:
        'In%20the%20MMO%20RPG%20%22Realm%20of%20the%20Mad%20God%22%2C%20what%20dungeon%20is%20widely%20considered%20to%20be%20the%20most%20difficult%3F',
      correct_answer: 'The%20Shatter%27s',
      incorrect_answers: [
        'Snake%20Pit',
        'The%20Tomb%20of%20the%20Acient%27s',
        'The%20Puppet%20Master%27s%20Theater',
      ],
    },
    {
      category: 'Entertainment%3A%20Music',
      type: 'multiple',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      question: 'When%20did%20the%20rapper%20Eazy-E%20die%3F',
      correct_answer: 'March%2026%2C%201995',
      incorrect_answers: [
        'July%2011%2C%201992',
        'February%2014%2C%201993',
        'October%2021%2C%201994',
      ],
    },
  ],
}

export default SampleSet
